bhcosmetics.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy | Shop Beauty & Makeup Products | BH Cosmetics LLC

Last Updated: 10/15/2018 

BHCosmetics.com (the “Site”) is brought to you by BH Cosmetics, LLC (“we”, “us”, or “our”).  This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect on the Site, how it is used, to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  All other terms not defined herein will have the meanings herein will have the meanings set forth in our Terms and Conditions.  By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the policy, please do not use the Site.

To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we want to notify you of:

What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through this Site

  * Who is collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information we collect.

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

_Personal Information_

We collect personal information from you when you submit it to us, including by:

(1) registering on the Site;

(2) placing an order;

(3) signing up for our newsletter;

(4) contacting us; or

(5) participating in a Site promotion or survey.  This information may include your name, email address, address, telephone number, date of birth and credit card information.  We may combine the information we collect from you with information we receive about you from other sources, such as address update services. 

_Non - Personal Information_

When you visit the Site, we may collect certain non-personally- identifiable information from you, including your IP address, browser type, operating system and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. We may also collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other clickstream data.

We may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer when you access the Site. We may also use cookies to: 

(1) allow you to use the Site without having to re-enter your login information;

(2) enhance or personalize your Site usage and shopping experience;

(3) monitor Site usage;

(4) manage the Site; and

(5) improve the Site and our products and services.

You are free to decline cookies (opt out), but doing so may prevent you from using certain features on the Site. Check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

We may also use web beacons on the Site, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Site visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and / or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. We may also collect the URL of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Site. Web beacons help us analyze our Site visitors’ behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Site and our advertising. We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information.

We may use third - party advertising companies’ tracking technologies to serve our advertisement across the Internet. These companies may collect anonymous information about your visits to the Site and other websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications.

We may combine the non - personal information we collect through cookies and web beacons with other information we have collected from you.

USE OF INFORMATION

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

(1) to fulfill your requests for products;

(2) to respond to your inquiries;

(3) to contact you with Site updates, newsletters and other informational and promotional material from us and third - party marketing offers from our trusted partners;

(4) to contact you when necessary (please note that if you opt-out of marketing communications, we may still contact your regarding administrative or service-related issues);

(5) to review site usage and operations;

(6) to address problems with the Site, our business or our services; and

(7) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business. You may choose not to receive promotional email from us by following the unsubscribe(opt-out) instructions in each message.

For personal data that is subject to General Data Protective Regulation 2016/679 (“GDPR”), we rely on several legal bases to use and process your personal data, which include (i) when you have given consent, which you may withdraw at any time by using [PROVIDE METHOD TO DELETE, e.g., hyperlink to ACCOUNT SETTINGS or sending email to support@bhcosmetics.com]; (ii) when data processing is necessary to perform a contract with you, such as the Terms and Conditions, and (iii) our legitimate business interests, such as improving and personalizing the Services, marketing new features or products that may be of  interest to you, and promoting safety and security of the Site and our Customers.

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers to perform   business, professional or technical support functions for us;

(2) as necessary if we believe there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party;

(3) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety as permitted or required by law; and

(4) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent. We may share aggregate, non - personally identifiable information about Site users with third parties.

Please note that any personal information that you voluntarily submit for posting to the Site (such as to a blog) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.  **If you chose to voluntarily disclose personal information in a public forum on the Site or link to your account profile, that information will be considered public information and the protections of this Privacy Policy will not apply.**  

ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We give you account settings and tools to access and control your personal data regardless of where you live.  If you live in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, and Switzerland (“Designated Region”), you have several legal rights regarding your information as discussed below.  

Accessing Data.  You may access your personal information by signing into your account. From there you can correct or modify your information.

Exporting Data.  If you live in the Designated Region, by logging into your account, you may access your personal information and you can also download your personal information in a common file format.  

Deleting Data.  If you live in the Designated Region, you can change or delete your personal information in your account settings.  Additionally, you may delete your account if you wish.  We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your requests for deletion, but certain information will actively persist on the Site even if you close your account, including messages you posted on our Site.  In addition, personal information may remain in our archives and information you update or delete, or information within a closed account, may persist internally for our administrative purposes, legal compliance reasons, to the extent permitted by law.  In addition, we typically do not remove information you posted publicly through or on our Site.  Please note that you or BH Cosmetics can delete all copies of information that has been previously shared with others on our Site.    

Objecting or Restricting Data Use.  In your account settings, you have options to control our use of your data.  You may limit how your information is visible to other users or made publicly available; and limit the notifications or emails you receive from us.  Please note that should you opt-out of receiving notifications or emails from us, you will still receive administrative messages from us.  If you are receiving texts sent via the Service and you wish to opt out, reply STOP to any such message, or send an email with your cellphone number and the subject line “Opt-Out” to support@bhcosmetics.com.

If you live in a Designated Region, you have the right to object to our processing of your information based on our legitimate interests and the right to object to the use of your information for direct marketing purposes.  You may control our marketing communications to you by accessing your account settings.  Additionally, you should review our USE OF INFORMATION section for your options to control how we use cookies and other technologies for advertising.  Please note that you can delete your account at any time if you do not want us to use or process your information.

DATA RETENTION

We keep your information, such as your name, email address and phone number for as long as you keep your account in existence.  In some instances, we will delete the information you provide to us after it is no longer needed.  We also keep information about you and your use of the Site for long as it is necessary for our legitimate business interests, for legal reasons, and to prevent harm to you, any third party, or us.

INTERNATIONAL USERS AND DATA TRANSFERS

If you are located outside of the United States and choose to provide personal information to us, we transfer such personal information to the United States for processing and our service providers may process personal information in the United States or other locations.  These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country you provided the information.  When we transfer your information to the United States, we will protect it as described in this Privacy Policy. 

When we transfer personal information from the Designated Region to our service provides and affiliates in the United States, we rely on approved transfer mechanisms, including standard contract clauses approved by the European Commission.  You may request a copy of standard contractual clauses relevant to your personal information, if any, using the contact information below. 

By providing your information to the Site, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  If you wish to withdraw your consent, you can delete your account as described in the ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  section.

AFFILIATES

We may establish one or more affiliate programs. An affiliate program allows other websites to earn money by linking customers to our Site from their sites. These affiliates can only access data about the number of transactions and their resulting earnings. They cannot access our customers’ personal data.

WEBSITE EVALUATION, MARKETING, AND PROMOTIONS

We may engage third parties to assist in providing website evaluation services, marketing, order processing, fulfillment and shipping services, as well as customer service. We may engage third parties to provide services such as fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, data analysis and data cleansing. These third parties will have access to information on an as-needed basis only, and will be required not to use any personal information for any purpose other than providing such services.

SECURITY

We have taken physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to protect your personal information. The only time you are required to sign in on the website is when you are making a purchase. On the checkout page, you will be asked to access your existing account or create a new one. Existing account holders are prompted for their email address and password. This password is for your protection. If you don’t have your password, there is a link to instructions to retrieve your password.

DO NOT TRACK

Some web browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” feature. Because there is not yet an accepted standard for how to respond to Do Not Track signals, our website does not currently respond to such signals.

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Site may contain links to third - party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through the Site.

CHILDREN

The Site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age, or any higher minimum age in the jurisdiction where that person resides (“Child” or “Children”), and is not intentionally developed for or directed to Children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any information from Children nor do we knowingly market our products or services to Children. If we learn that we have collected information of a Child, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible and, if applicable, terminate that Child’s account. 

POLICY CHANGES

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on our website. If we change the policy significantly, we will provide appropriate online notice to you.

YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California law permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. This request is free and may be made once a year. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

BH Cosmetics, LLC

ATTN: Customer Service Department

2801 Burton Ave.

Burbank, CA 91504

COMPLAINTS

While we hope that you will not need to, if you want to complain about our use of Personal Information please send an email detailing your complaint with the subject line “Personal Information Complaint" to support@bhcosmetics.com.

If you reside in the European Economic Area, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority. Please see further details below:

UK

| 

Information Commissioner’s Office

Wycliffe House, Water Lane

Wilmslow

Cheshire

SK9 5AFwww.ico.org.uk

Tel: 0303 123 1113

Tel:  029 2067 8400 (calls in Welsh)

Email: casework@ico.org.uk  
  
---|---  
  
Germany

| 

Spain

| 

Spanish Data Protection Agency at:

Calle Jorge Juan, 6

28001

Madrid

Or via https://sedeagpd.gob.es/sede-electronica-web/  
  
Italy

| 

Garante per la protezione dei data personali

Piazza di Monte Citorio n. 121

00186

Romawww.gpdp.it –  www.garanteprivacy.it

E-mail: urp@gpdp.it

Fax: (+39) 06.69677.3785

Centralino telefonico: (+39) 06.69677.1  
  
Belgium

| 

Commission for the Protection of Privacy

Rue de la Presse 35

1000 BrusselsTel: +32 (0)2 274 48 00

Fax: +32 (0)2 274 48 35

commission@privacycommission.be  
  
France

| 

Commission Nationale de l’Informatique et des Libertés

3 Place de Fontenoy

TSA 80715 – 75334

PARIS CEDEX 07Tél : 01 53 73 22 22(du lundi au jeudi de 9h à 18h30 / le vendredi de 9h à 18h)

Fax : 01 53 73 22 00

Online form for complaints: https://www.cnil.fr/fr/plaintes  
  
Netherlands

| 

Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens

Postbus 93374

2509 AJ DEN HAAGTel: (+31) – (0)70 – 888 85 00

Fax: (+31) – (0)70 – 888 85 01  
  
Sweden

| 

Datainspektionen

Box 8114

SE-104 20 StockholmSweden Office address:Drottninggatan 29, 5th floor

StockholmE-mail: datainspektionen@datainspektionen.se

Tel:  +46 8 657 61 00  
  
CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, contact us at support@bhcosmetics.com
